socialstreets.com 2012-12-30

# United States SocialStreets

|  |   
---|---|---  
| 

Privacy Policy

What information do we collect?

  1. We collect information from you when you register on our site or fill out a form. 
  2. When registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: full name, e-mail address, mailing address or phone number.
  3. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.  
Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 
  1. To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  2. To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  3. To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
  4. To process transactions. 
  5. Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the service requested. 
  6. To send you targeted emails, service update notices, and promotional offers based on your communication preferences
  7. To prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities, and enforce our Terms of Service

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

How do we protect your information?

  1. We store and process your personal information on our servers in the US and Canada, and we protect it by maintaining physical, electronic and procedural safeguards in compliance with applicable US and Canadian federal regulations. We use firewalls and data encryption, we enforce physical access controls to our facilities.
  2. We encrypt our cookies so that only we can interpret the information stored in them. You are free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, but doing so may interfere with your use of our website.We may also collect information about your computer or other access device to mitigate risk and for fraud prevention purposes.

Do we use cookies?

  1. Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information
  2. We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

  1. We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
  2. We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

Terms of Service

Please also visit our Terms of Service section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at <http://www.socialstreets.com/docs/terms_of_service.html>.

Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.  

Changes to our Privacy Policy

  1. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, send an email notifying you of any changes, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. 
  2. This policy was last modified on 10-10-2007
  3. Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information found at the link below.  
<http://www.socialstreets.com/docs/contact.html>  

|   
|  |
